Privacy Policy for Senbilcloud
==============================

Last updated: Agust 12, 2022

This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.

We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy

We do not sell your data. We collect your data to make our service work, to save your preferences and to protect ourself from attacks.

Interpretation and Definitions
==============================

Interpretation
--------------

The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.

Definitions
-----------

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:

* **Account** means a unique account created for You to access our Service or parts of our Service.
    
* **Company** (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to Senbilcloud.
    
* **Cookies** are small files that are placed on Your computer, mobile device or any other device by a website, containing the details of Your browsing history on that website among its many uses.
    
* **Country** refers to: Turkey
    
* **Device** means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone or a digital tablet.
    
* **Personal Data** is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.
    
* **Service** refers to the Website.
    
* **Service Provider** means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Company. It refers to third-party companies or individuals employed by the Company to facilitate the Service, to provide the Service on behalf of the Company, to perform services related to the Service or to assist the Company in analyzing how the Service is used.
    
* **Usage Data** refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
    
* **Website** refers to Senbilcloud, accessible from [https://cloud.senbil.net](https://cloud.senbil.net/) [https://bulut.senbil.net](https://bulut.senbil.net/) [https://okul.senbil.net](https://okul.senbil.net/) [https://awscdn.senbil.net](https://cdn.senbil.net/) [https://cdn.senbil.net](https://awscdn.senbil.net/) [https://ozgurtarifler.senbil.net](https://ozgurtarifler.senbil.net/) [https://auth.senbil.net](https://auth.senbil.net/) [https://meet.senbil.net](https://meet.senbil.net/) and all sites that end with senbil.net
    
* **You** means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.
    
* **IP Adress** An IP address is a unique address that identifies a device on the internet or a local network. IP addresses are the identifier that allows information to be sent between devices on a network: they contain location information and make devices accessible for communication. The internet needs a way to differentiate between different computers, routers, and websites. IP addresses provide a way of doing so and form an essential part of how the internet works.

Collecting and Using Your Personal Data
=======================================

Types of Data Collected
-----------------------

### Personal Data

While using Our Service, We may ask You to provide Us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify You. Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Usage Data

### Usage Data

Usage Data is collected automatically when using the Service.

Usage Data may include information such as Your Device's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that You visit, the time and date of Your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers, your operating system and other diagnostic data.

When You access the Service by or through a mobile device, We may collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device You use, Your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of Your mobile device, Your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser You use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

We may also collect information that Your browser sends whenever You visit our Service or when You access the Service by or through a mobile device.

* Information you provide to us

Account information. When you create a SenbilCloud account , you can come up with a username and password, and provide a way of contacting you (such as an email address and/or phone number).

Content you create. This includes any content that you upload to the service. For example, you may write messages (including drafts), upload and share files through the services. We generally do not store the contents of video or voice calls (but do store text messages in all SenbilCloud services) in SenbilCloud-Jitsi-Meet there is a visiual indication of recording similir to Zoom software

### Cookies

We use Cookies to save The technologies We use may include:

* **Cookies or Browser Cookies.** A cookie is a small file placed on Your Device. You can instruct Your browser to refuse all Cookies or to indicate when a Cookie is being sent. However, if You do not accept Cookies, You may not be able to use some parts of our Service. Unless you have adjusted Your browser setting so that it will refuse Cookies, our Service may use Cookies.
* **We use some them to prevent CSRF attacks. No identifable information is stored in those.**

**

Cookies can be "Persistent" or "Session" Cookies. Persistent Cookies remain on Your personal computer or mobile device when You go offline, while Session Cookies are deleted as soon as You close Your web browser. Learn more about cookies: [Cookies: What Do They Do?](https://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/blog/cookies/).

We use Persistent Cookies for the purposes set out below:

* **Functionality Cookies**
    
    Type: Persistent Cookies
    
    Administered by: Us
    
    Purpose: These Cookies allow us to remember choices You make when You use the Website, such as remembering your login details or language preference. The purpose of these Cookies is to provide You with a more personal experience and to avoid You having to re-enter your preferences every time You use the Website.
    
    **Information about Cloudflare cookies [https://support.cloudflare.com/hc/en-us/articles/200170156-Understanding-the-Cloudflare-Cookies](https://support.cloudflare.com/hc/en-us/articles/200170156-Understanding-the-Cloudflare-Cookies)**

For more information about the cookies we use and your choices regarding cookies, please visit our Cookies Policy or the Cookies section of our Privacy Policy.

Use of Your Personal Data
-------------------------

The Company may use Personal Data for the following purposes:

* **To provide and maintain our Service**, including to monitor the usage of our Service.
    
    **To analyze users**We use a self hosted version of matomo an open source analytics platform that is located at https://analytics.senbil.net/ matomo does not use any cookies and anonimizes ip adressses. You can disable the tracking either by sending a do not track message or blocking https://analytics.senbil.net/ on your computer/network/dns resolver
    
    The data we collect to analyze users : Anonimsed IP Adressses, Your country and the city/state you live in, Information about your browser for example the product name Crome and version 80, Information about your computer for example your operating system your screen size. The pages you visit and how long you have stayed there where you came to a SenbilCloud web page for example from Google
    
    Analytics are disabled on p.senbil.net
    
* **To manage Your Account:** to manage Your registration as a user of the Service. The Personal Data You provide can give You access to different functionalities of the Service that are available to You as a registered user.
    
* To provide you with the services. We use your information to provide you with the SenbilCloud services. For example, when you start a video call or join a meeting, we process your images and audio to make that work. We similarly collect and store the messages you send and display them as you direct.
    
* To protect our services. We use information to keep our services secure, to prevent misuse, and to enforce our Terms of Service and other policies against users who violate them.
    
* To improve our services. We use your information to help us understand how users interact with our services, what features or products users may want, or to otherwise understand and improve our services. This includes information about how you use our services and how servers are structured.
    
* To contact you. We use your information to contact you in connection with your account, such as to verify or secure it with two-factor authentication. We may also use your information to contact you about important product or policy changes, to send you information about products you have purchased, or just to let you know about new products or features we think you’ll like. You may opt-out (by sending a email to mail@senbil.net) of receiving marketing communications. Where local law requires, we will obtain your consent before sending such communications.
    
* ### Traffic optimization and distribution

This type of service allows this Application to distribute their content using servers located across different countries and to optimize their performance. Which Personal Data are processed depends on the characteristics and the way these services are implemented. Their function is to filter communications between this Application and the User's browser. Considering the widespread distribution of this system, it is difficult to determine the locations to which the contents that may contain Personal Information of the User are transferred. Cloudflare (Cloudflare Inc.) [https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/](https://www.cloudflare.com/privacypolicy/) Cloudflare is a traffic optimization and distribution service provided by Cloudflare Inc. The way Cloudflare is integrated means that it filters all the traffic through this Application, i.e., communication between this Application and the User's browser, while also allowing analytical data from this Application to be collected. Personal Data processed: various types of Data as specified in the privacy policy of the service. Place of processing: United States – Privacy Policy.

Retention of Your Personal Data
-------------------------------

The Company will retain Your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use Your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

The Company will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of Our Service, or We are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

Transfer of Your Personal Data
------------------------------

Your information, including Personal Data, is processed at the Company's operating offices and in any other places where the parties involved in the processing are located. It means that this information may be transferred to and maintained on computers located outside of Your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from Your jurisdiction.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by Your submission of such information represents Your agreement to that transfer.

The Company will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that Your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of Your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of Your data and other personal information.

Disclosure of Your Personal Data
--------------------------------

### Law enforcement

Under certain circumstances, the Company may be required to disclose Your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Other legal requirements

The Company may disclose Your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* Comply with a legal obligation
* Protect and defend the rights or property of the Company
* Prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* Protect the personal safety of Users of the Service or the public
* Protect against legal liability

* Countries where your personal data will be transferred and stored
* We use Cloudflare, Cloudflare is a global network of over 200 servers around the world
* The full list of Cloudflare server locations https://www.cloudflare.com/network/
* Your data will also be stored and procsesed in: Turkey, Holland, Germany, France, Switzerland

Security of Your Personal Data
------------------------------

The security of Your Personal Data is important to Us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While We strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect Your Personal Data, We cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Links to Other Websites
=======================

Our Service may contain links to other websites that are not operated by Us. If You click on a third party link, You will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise You to review the Privacy Policy of every site You visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Changes to this Privacy Policy
==============================

We may update Our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify You of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let You know via email and/or a prominent notice on Our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "Last updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us
==========

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, You can contact us:

* By email: [\[email protected\]](https://privacy.senbil.net/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

**

**Privacy Policy for Senbilcloud

**
